pleasantholidays.com 2019-03-27

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us and we take it very seriously. This Privacy Statement applies to online transactions conducted within the United States on Pleasant Holidays.com and Pleasant Agent.com (hereinafter referred to as "Pleasant Holidays," "we," "us," or "our"). This Statement does not apply to companies that Pleasant Holidays does not own or control, or to people we do not manage or employ. For the privacy policy of web sites outside of PleasantHolidays.com and PleasantAgent.com, please see their web site for their policy.

This Privacy Statement sets forth our practice regarding the collection, use and protection of your Personal Information. Personal Information includes your name, residence address, date of birth, e-mail, telephone numbers and payment card information. By visiting our site, you are accepting the Privacy Statement described herein.

**Information Protection and Website Security**  
Protecting your information while you visit our website is important to us. We protect your Personal Information by restricting access to those employees who need to know. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard your Personal Information.

We want users of our website to feel confident and comfortable planning and purchasing travel with us. Firewalls and secure servers provide protection. Customer data is transferred securely using industry standard Certificate Authority verified encryption provided by Network Solutions. While not every page that collects Personal Information is encrypted, pages collecting payment card information including payment card number, card type, cardholder name and expiration date are encrypted.

**What Information We Collect From You**  
We collect Personal Information to provide travel products and services to you. You are not required to provide any Personal Information when browsing our site unless and until you make a purchase or sign-up for our e-mail newsletters or other services described below. A valid payment card is required to make a purchase on our site. Personal Information is collected when you voluntarily and specifically provide it. Our site is intended for use by persons 18 years of age or older and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from minors (those under 18 years of age). When you purchase travel arrangements for someone else through our site, we will request Personal Information about that individual. You should obtain the consent of other individuals prior to providing us with their Personal Information. We may also request information about your travel preferences such as frequent flyer/hotel program information, airline choice or cabin options.

**Making a Purchase  
** A valid payment card is required to make a purchase. To purchase travel and related services, you must provide your full name including middle name or initial, gender, date of birth (as well as the full names, gender and date of birth of others accompanying you), residence street address, e-mail address, telephone numbers, TSA Redress Number (if any), travel agency identification number and payment card information including card number, card type, cardholder name, expiration date and card verification number. You must obtain the consent of other individuals who may accompany you prior to providing their names, as they may be unable to view, change, cancel or modify any information you provide on their behalf. We may also request the name of the travel provider (e.g., airline) you will use, airline flight numbers, frequent flyer programs and other frequent program numbers. We require this information so that we can process, fulfill and confirm your reservations and transactions. When you purchase travel with us, you will receive confirmation of your travel itinerary via e-mail.

**Pleasant Travel Club**  
As a convenience to our customers, you have the option of creating a profile and preferences on our website which can be accessed in the future and used when making new bookings. Personal Information you add to your profile and preferences may include your full name, including middle name or initial, gender, date of birth, passport information (as well as the full names, gender, date of birth and passport information of others accompanying you), residence street address, e-mail address and telephone numbers. You can return to our site and edit your profile and preferences online.

**Travel Agency Account Profiles**  
Travel agencies conducting business with us on PleasantAgent.com have the option of creating an agency profile on our website. Personal Information you can add to your profile may include your full name, including middle name or initial, gender, date of birth, street address, telephone numbers, fax number and travel agency identification number. You can return to our site and edit your profile online.

**Sweepstakes and Promotions**  
We may offer visitors to our site the opportunity to participate in promotions, contests or sweepstakes. Information collected when you participate in a promotion, contest or sweepstake may include your full name, residence address, telephone number and e-mail address.

**Surveys**  
We may offer visitors the opportunity to participate in surveys. You are under no obligation to respond to any survey, and you may unsubscribe from receiving any survey sent via e-mail by following the unsubscribe instructions in the survey you receive. Information collected when you participate in a survey may include your full name, residence address, telephone numbers, age category, household income range, travel preferences, travel agency identification number and e-mail addresses.

**Employment Purposes**  
Personal Information, including your full name, residence address, telephone numbers, e-mail, gender, employment history and educational background will be collected when you apply online for employment with us. The retention period for applications is one year.

**TSA Secure Flight Program**  
Privacy Notice (as required under 49 U.S.C. § 1560.13): The Transportation Security Administration of the U.S. Department of Homeland Security requires us to collect information from you for purposes of watch list screening, under the authority of 49 U.S.C. section 114, and the Intelligence Reform and Terrorism Prevention Act of 2004. Providing this information is voluntary; however, if it is not provided, you may be subject to additional screening or denied transport or authorization to enter a sterile area. TSA may share information you provide with law enforcement or intelligence agencies or others under its published system of records notice. For more on TSA Privacy policies, or to view the system of records notice and the privacy impact assessment, please see TSA's Web site at [wwww.tsa.gov](https://www.tsa.gov/).

The information we are required to collect under the Secure Flight Program includes: full name (as it appears on the passenger’s government-issued identification document used when traveling), date of birth, gender and TSA Redress Number (if available).

**How We Use Information We Collect**  
We use the Personal Information we collect for many purposes including completing your travel purchase; sending you special travel promotions, travel tips and general information; communicating with you about your travel plans; notifying you in the event of itinerary changes; providing travel documents; sending you e-mails; preventing prohibited or illegal activities; enforcing company policies and agreements including Terms and Conditions of Sale and User Agreement; providing you with information about our other travel brands; for employment purposes; improving your overall experience when visiting our site for our own internal purposes and for conducting business with travel agency and affiliate partners.

**Itinerary Modifications** From time to time, modifications may be made to your travel itinerary due to unforeseen schedule changes and business conditions. When such modifications are made, you may be notified by e-mail, telephone and/or postal mail to inform you of these modifications and help you make alternative arrangements, if necessary.

**With Whom We Share Your Information**  
To process and provide the travel services you request and purchase, we may share your Personal Information with our third-party travel providers, such as airlines, hotels, car rental companies, ground transportation, cruise, activity and travel protection plan providers, who fulfill your travel reservations on our behalf. These third-party travel providers may need information about your profile to process and facilitate your travel reservation. Personal Information shared may include full name including middle name or initial, gender, date of birth (as well as the full names, gender and date of birth of others accompanying you) and TSA Redress Number (if any). We do not place limitations on their use or disclosure of your Personal Information. You are encouraged to review the privacy policies of any such travel provider whose products you consider purchasing through our site. We may also share Personal Information among our affiliated companies.

We use third-party vendors who provide services or functions on our behalf including credit card processing, marketing, e-mails, newsletters, surveys and sweepstakes. We contractually limit their use of your Personal Information for the purposes for which it is provided.

We partner with third-party sites to offer you additional services. To process and confirm your travel reservations and/or purchases, our third-party partners may also collect Personal Information including your name, residence address, telephone numbers, date of birth, payment card information and e-mail address. We do not manage or control the privacy policies of these third-party business partners and encourage you to review the privacy policies of third-party partner sites whose services you consider using.

When required by law, legal process, or government, we may disclose information we have collected from visitors when they purchase travel products or services, or apply for employment. In certain cases involving fraud or illegal activities, we may disclose information to investigate, prevent or protect our interests, property, or safety of employees or customers. Additionally, it may become necessary to provide customer information to payment card companies, for the purpose of resolving chargebacks or disputes that arise in the normal course of business.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
When you visit our site, we may assign a “cookie” (a small, unique identifier text file) and a web beacon (a small transparent image file) which is very common on the Internet. You do not provide this information, as it is collected automatically and used in a variety of ways to optimize visits to our site, including the use of third-party services for improving the user’s overall site experience. The cookie and web beacon do not contain any Personal Information, but collect your IP address. You have the ability not to receive a cookie file and to disable a web beacon by enabling your Web Browser to refuse cookies or prompt you before accepting a cookie. The vast majority of visitors to our site leave their cookies enabled, and those refusing to accept cookies may not have access to certain tools, services and/or features offered by our site. You may also manually delete cookie files from your computer’s hard drive.

When you visit this website, third parties, including advertising partners, analytics providers and ad servers that utilize Floodlight Tags may collect information about your online activity over time and across websites. A Floodlight Tag is a tracking tag for DoubleClick platforms that is typically used to measure conversions resulting from users seeing or interacting with certain ads.

We use third party advertising networks to serve ads on our behalf across the internet. These companies employ cookies, pixels and web beacons to gather information (such as purchase behavior and user attributes) that permits us to analyze, modify, and improve our advertising content. The information collected is not personally identifiable. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features these third party advertising networks may use, and their information practices are not covered by this Privacy Statement.

**Tracking**  
We do not respond to a web browser's "Do Not Track" signal. Such a signal enables a person to opt out from having information about their web browsing activities monitored and collected; however, since there is not uniform industry agreement as to how to respond, we do not currently honor such a request.

**Your California Privacy Rights**  
Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of personal information the business shares with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year.

To request a copy of the information disclosure we provide pursuant to this requirement, please refer to the Contact Information section below.

**Changes to Our Privacy Statement**  
We may amend this Privacy Statement at any time. Please review this site periodically. Any changes are effective upon our posting of the revised Statement as of the Effective Date. Your use of our website following any such change constitutes acceptance.

**Contact Information** If you have questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Statement, or if you need further assistance, please contact us at 2404 Townsgate Road, Westlake Village CA 91361.

Thank you for taking the time to read this Privacy Policy and for using PleasantHolidays.com or PleasantAgent.com.

**Effective Date: January 30, 2017**
